http://www.stepfamily.org/privacy-policy.html

Follow us on:
Certification Seminar
Who should attend the certification seminar?
Why should I become a Stepfamily Foundation Certified Counselor or Coach?
What are the Benefits of Certification?
What will I receive at the Stepfamily Certification Seminar?
What information do we collect? We
collect information from you when you register on our site, place an
order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a
form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate,
you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address,
phone number, credit card information or social security number. You
may, however, visit our site anonymously.Google, as a third
party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users
based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google
ad and content network privacy policy..What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To process transactionsYour
information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged,
transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever,
without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering
the purchased product or service requested.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site featureTo send periodic emailsThe
email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you
information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to
receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service
information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to
unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed
unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information? We
implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or
access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure
server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via
Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment
gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized
with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the
information confidential.After a transaction, your private
information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.)
will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.Do we use cookies? Yes
(Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)
that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information We use
cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart,
understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of
advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site
interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in
the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist
us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers
are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except
to help us conduct and improve our business.If you prefer, you
can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being
sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser
settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our
services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders
over the telephone or by contacting customer service.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this
information confidential. We may also release your information when we
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided
to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party
products or services on our website. These third party sites have
separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no
responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these
linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site
and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause
we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in
compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We
therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside
parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We
are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online
Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and Conditions Please
also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use,
disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our
website at http://www.stepfamily.orgYour Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If
we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on
this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the
Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on 08/27/2013Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. http://www.stepfamily.org310 W.85th Street, Suite 1B New York, New York 10024USAstepfamilyfoundation@gmail.com1-212-877-3244This policy is powered by Trust Guard, your PCI compliance authority.
The Stepfamily Foundation Inc.310 W.85th StreetNew York, NY 10024(212)877-3244(646)789-2525Email: stepfamilyfoundation@gmail.comWebmaster: webmaster@stepfamily.org
Sign Up For Our Newsletter!
Stay connected by signing up for our newsletter on our latest updates, articles, events and more!
Sign Up NowFor Email Marketing you can trust.
Copyright ©
The Stepfamily Foundation Inc.
Site design by Red Lotus Designz
